Pelke, Bill; Papers apap205
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1974-2003, Undated; 2; 1.15 cubic feet
  - Los Angeles Reader, September 29, 1995 (Oversize 7, Folder 4)
  - Loyola University Chicago Law Journal, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 56)
  - Mandala, 2000 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 57)
  - The Messenger, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 58)
  - National Catholic Reader, March 31, 1989 (Oversize 7, Folder 5)
  - Ne Deja Vu Pas- A Collection of Poetr y - by Trovatore Poetaster, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 59)
  - " The New Creature in Christ " - Bilble Study Series by Mark D. Fronkiewicz and William J. Kitchens, Undated (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 60)
  - New York, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 61)
  - " New Yorkers want an Alternative to the Death Penalty ", by William J. Bowers and Margaret Vandiver, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 62)
  - Newsweek, 1990 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 63)
  - Northeastern University Press - New Books, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 64)
  - Notre Dame Magazine, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 65)
  - OGGI, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 66)
  - " The O. J. Simpson Case and Capital Punishment " - Howard Law Journal, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 67)
  - The Only Voice, June, 1993 (Oversize 7, Folder 6)
  - The Orlando Sentinel, April 19, 1998 (Oversize 7, Folder 7)
  - The Other Side, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 68)
  - The Other Side, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 69)
  - The Other Side, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 70)
  - The Other Side, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 71)
  - The Other Side's - Faces of Faith, 1990 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 72)
  - The Philadelphia Inquirer, October 4, 1987 (Oversize 7, Folder 8)
  - The Philadelphia Inquirer, September 18, 1994 (Oversize 7, Folder 9)
  - The Philadelphia Trumpet, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 73)
  - The Philadelphia Trumpet, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 74)
  - The Philadelphia Trumpet, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 75)
  - The Philadelphia Trumpet, 1999 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 76)
  - " The Possible Pain Experienced During Execution by Different Methods ", 1993 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 77)
  - " Promoting Mutual Forgiveness within the Fractured Relationship " by Everett L. Worthington, Jr., 1990 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 78)
  - " Question of Violation of Human Rights and Fundamental Freedoms " - Commission on Human Rights, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 79)
  - " Refocusing the Death Penalty Discussion in America " - American Bar Association, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 80)
  - " Security the Soul on the Death Penalty ", 1998 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 81)
  - SPIN, November, 1991 (Oversize 7, Folder 10)
  - The Story the time Couldn't tell - Church of Scientology, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 82)
  - Ten Basic Responsibilities of Nonprofit Boards by Richard T. Ingram, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 83)
  - Thomas M. Cooley Law Review - Death Penalty Symposium, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 84)
  - Time, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 85)
  - We, On Death Row, 2000 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 86)
  - The White House Report to students, ca.1985 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 87)
  - Whole Life Times, April, 1995 (Oversize 7, Folder 11)
  - " Yeah, Clementine ", by H.L. " Willie " Otey, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 88)
- MVFR/Journey of Hope, 1990-2007, Undated; 3; 3.26 cubic feet
  This series contains supplemental material to the Murder Victims Families For Reconciliation Records collected by Bill Pelke during his tenure as a board member of that organization. Included in this series are administrative records, correspondence, promotional materials, documents relating to Bill Pelkes time as editor of MVFRs newsletter The Voice including drafts and layouts, and folders relating to the Journey of Hope events from 1993-1999 assembled by Bill Pelke.
  - Appearance on "Playing Defense" Program hosted by Rex Lamont Butler, 2007 (Oversize 9, Dvd 1)
  - Correspondence, 1991; 1993-1994; 1998; Undated (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 1)
  - Journey of Hope, 1993 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 2)
  - Journey of Hope, 1994 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 3)
  - Journey of Hope, 1995 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 4)
  - Journey of Hope, 1997 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 5)
  - Journey of Hope, 1998 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 6)
  - Journey of Hope, 1998 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 7)
  - Journey of Hope, 1999 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 8)
  - Journey of Hope, Undated (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 9)
  - Journey of Hope - Articles of Incorporation, 1998 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 10)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 1993 (Oversize 3, Item 1)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 1995 (Oversize 3, Item 3)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 1998 (Oversize 2, Item 2)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 2000 (Oversize 2, Item 4)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 2001 (Oversize 1, Item 1)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 2001 (Oversize 1, Item 2)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 2003 (Oversize 1, Item 3)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 2005 (Oversize 1, Item 4)
  - Journey of Hope - Bumper Sticker, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 14)
  - Journey of Hope - Business Card, Undated (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 11)
  - Journey of Hope - Button, 1993 (Oversize 5, Item 7)
  - Journey of Hope - Button, 1994 (Oversize 5, Item 8)
  - Journey of Hope - Button, 1998 (Oversize 5, Item 9)
  - Journey of Hope - California Journey Account, 1996 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 12)
  - Journey of Hope - Conference Call, May 23, 1995 (Oversize 9, Cassette 2)
  - Journey of Hope - Final Night Video (part 1), October 16, 1996 (Oversize 9, Vhs 1)
  - Journey of Hope - Final Night Video (part 2), October 16, 1996 (Oversize 9, Vhs 2)
  - Journey of Hope - Georgia Packet, 1994 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 13)
  - Journey of Hope - Georgia Packet, 1994 (Box 1 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 14)
  - Journey of Hope - Gray T-shirt, 1996 (Oversize 2, Item 1)
  - Journey of Hope - Members, 1993 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 1)
  - Journey of Hope - Notes, 1995 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 2)
  - Journey of Hope - Organizing Handbook, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 3)
  - Journey of Hope - Organizing Handbook, Undated (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 4)
  - Journey of Hope - Poster, 1993 (Flat-file 5)
  - Journey of Hope - Press Packet, 2003 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 5)
  - Journey of Hope - Promotional Material, 1993-1994 (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
  - Journey of Hope - White T-shirt, 1994 (Oversize 3, Item 2)
  - Journey of Hope - White T-shirt, 1995 (Oversize 3, Item 4)
  - Journey of Hope - White T-shirt, 1999 (Oversize 2, Item 3)
  - MVFR - ACLU Letter to Congress, 1994 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 6)
  - MVFR - Business Card Holder, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 5)
  - MVFR - Business Cards, Undated (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 7)
  - MVFR - Board, 1990 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 8)
  - MVFR - Board, 1993 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 9)
  - MVFR - Board, 1994 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 10)
  - MVFR - Board, 1995 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 11)
  - MVFR - Board, 1996 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 12)
  - MVFR - Board, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 13)
  - MVFR - Board, Undated (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 14)
  - MVFR - By- Laws, Undated (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 15)
  - MVFR - Constitutional Amendment, 1996 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 16)
  - MVFR - Dead Man Walking Concert, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 17)
  - MVFR - Directors Report, 1996 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 18)
  - MVRF - Drafts, 1992-1993; 1995; Undated (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 19)
  - MVRF - Drafts, 1992-1994; 1996; Undated (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 20)
  - MVRF - Finances, 1992 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 21)
  - MVRF - Finances, 1993 (Box 2 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 22)
  - MVFR - Finances, 1994 (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 1)
  - MVFR - Finances, 1995 (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 2)
  - MVFR - Finances, 1998 (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 3)
  - MVFR - Internships, 1993 (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 4)
  - MVFR - Mailing Lists, Undated (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 5)
  - MVFR - Members List, Undated (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 6)
  - MVFR - Membership Committee, Undated (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 7)
  - MVFR - Mission Statement, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 8)
  - MVFR - " Not in Our Name ", 1998-1999 (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 9)
  - MVFR - Pelke Notes, Undated (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 10)
  - MVFR - Petition Form - Blank, Undated (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 11)
  - MVFR - Press Conference, 1994 (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 12)
  - MVFR - Promotional Material, 1993; Undated (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 13)
  - MVFR - Restorative Justice Proposal, Undated (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 14)
  - MVFR- The Voice, 1992 (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
  - MVFR- The Voice, 1994 (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 15)
  - MVFR- The Voice, 1995 (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 16)
  - MVFR- The Voice, 1997 (Box 3 (3-MVFR/Journey of Hope), Folder 17)
  - MVFR - The Voice Draft, 1992 (Oversize 7, Folder 3)
  - MVFR - Wooden Ornament, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 1)
  - MVFR - Wooden Ornament, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 2)
  - MVFR - Wooden Ornament, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 3)
  - MVFR - Wooden Ornament, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 4)
- Amnesty International, 1988-2000, Undated; 4; 3.75 cubic feet
  This series documents Bill Pelkes involvement in Amnesty International. Included in this sub-series are Amnesty International and Amnesty International USA (AIUSA) documents related to Bill Pelkes role as Indianas State Death Penalty Abolition Coordinator, newsletters, annual conference documents, annual reports, correspondence, flyers, pamphlets, and other outreach materials collected by Bill Pelke.
  - The ABC's of Abolition, Undated (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 1)
  - Abolition Network News, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 2)
  - Action Alert, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 3)
  - Action Alert on Federal Death Penalty, Undated (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 4)
  - The Activator, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 5)
  - The Activator, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 6)
  - The Activator, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 7)
  - The Activator, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 8)
  - The Activator, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 9)
  - The Activator, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 10)
  - Activity and Campaign Calendar for 1995-1996 (Oversize 8, Folder 1)
  - Amnesty Action, 1989; 1992-1994 (Oversize 8, Folder 2)
  - Amnesty Action Bulletin Board, Undated (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 11)
  - The Amnesty Break, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 12)
  - AIMLL: Amnesty International Membersz for Lesbian and Gay Concerns, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 13)
  - Amnesty International Policy Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 14)
  - Amnesty Now, 1997-2000 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 15)
  - Analysis of 1994 Local Group Activity, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 16)
  - Annual Action File Report, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 17)
  - Annual Conference, Undated (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 18)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 19)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 20)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 21)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 22)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 23)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 24)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 25)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 26)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 27)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 28)
  - Annual General Meeting, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 29)
  - Annual Local Group Report, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 30)
  - Annual Report, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 31)
  - Annual Report, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 32)
  - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 33)
  - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 34)
  - Appeals Cases, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 35)
  - Background Information World Conference on Human Rights, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 36)
  - Balkans Region, Undated (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 37)
  - Board of Directors, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 38)
  - Brochures, 1991-1997; Undated (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 39)
  - Budget and Bookkeeping Guidelines, ca.1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 40)
  - Budget and Bookkeeping Guidelines, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 41)
  - Budget and Bookkeeping Guidelines, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 42)
  - Bylaws, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 43)
  - Calendar, 1995-2000 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 44)
  - Calendar of Human Rights Events in Los Angeles, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 45)
  - Campaigns Against the Execution of Junvenile Offenders, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 46)
  - The Case of Mumia Abu - Jamal, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 47)
  - Casework Manual, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 48)
  - Challenge to Leadership, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 49)
  - China MFN Crisis Response, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 50)
  - Complaint Procedures Questionnaire, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 51)
  - Conditions for Death Row Prisoners in the H - Unit Oklahoma State Penitentiary, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 62)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 63)
  - Death Penalty Abolition Institute, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 64)
  - Death Penalty Abolitionists' Questionnaire from hell, Undated (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 65)
  - Death Penalty Actions, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 66)
  - Death Penalty Advisory Committee, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 67)
  - Death Penalty Director Research, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 68)
  - Death Penalty Education and Action Packet, ca.1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 69)
  - The Death Penalty in Texas, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 70)
  - Death Penalty Institute, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 71)
  - " Death Penalty is a Symbol not a Solution ", Undated (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 72)
  - Death Penalty Mailing, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 73)
  - Death Penalty Mailing, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 74)
  - Death Penalty Mailing, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 75)
  - Death Penalty Mailing, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 76)
  - Death Penalty Mailing, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 77)
  - AI USA - Death Penalty Newsletter, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 1)
  - AI USA - Death Penalty Newsletter, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 2)
  - AI USA - Death Penalty Newsletter, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 3)
  - AI USA - Death Penalty Newsletter, 1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 4)
  - Death Penalty Objectives, Midwest Region, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 5)
  - The Death Penalty Worldwide, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 6)
  - Developments on the Death Penalty During 1994, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 7)
  - Draft of Long Range Plan, ca.1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 8)
  - Election, 1992-1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 9)
  - Events Schedule, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 10)
  - " Execute Justice Not People ", Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 11)
  - Feedback Form, Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 12)
  - Finance Guidelines, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 13)
  - Finance Guidelines, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 14)
  - Financal Guidelines, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 15)
  - Flyers, 1991-1997; Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 16)
  - Focus, 1991; 1994 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 17)
  - Follow Up to Open Letter to President on the Death Penalty, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 18)
  - Form, letters, and petitions, 1991; 1993; 1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 19)
  - Freedom in the Balance, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 20)
  - French Group 186 - Against the Death Penalty Banner, Undated (Roll 1, Item 1)
  - Funding Amnesty's Human Rights work, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 21)
  - Fundraising for Human Rights, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 22)
  - Funds for Freedom, Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 23)
  - General, 1990-1997; Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 24)
  - General, 1990-1998; Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 25)
  - The Ginetta Sagan Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 26)
  - Group 22 Newsletter, 1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 27)
  - Haiti, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 28)
  - Help with Journey, Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 29)
  - Holiday Card Action, 1993-1995; 1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 30)
  - Human Rights and American Indians, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 31)
  - Human Rights and the Presidential Elections, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 32)
  - Human Rights and U.S. Security Assistance, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 33)
  - Human Rights Educators Network, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 34)
  - " Human Rights for Children ", Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 35)
  - Human Rights Have No Borders - Hat, Undated (Oversize 4, Item 2)
  - Human Rights Library, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 36)
  - Imminent Execution of Juvenile Offender (Update), 1993 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 37)
  - In Grant Placements, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 38)
  - Inside the Mandate, 1995; 1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 39)
  - Interact, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 40)
  - International Council Meeting, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 41)
  - International Week of Student Action, 1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 42)
  - Ivan Morris Fund, Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 43)
  - Job Announcements, 1992-1995; 1997; Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 44)
  - Leadership List, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 45)
  - Leadership Survey, Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 46)
  - Legislative Update, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 47)
  - Lillehaug Project, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 48)
  - The Lives Behind the Lies: The Campaign Against " Disappearances " and Political Killings, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 49)
  - Local Group Charter, Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 50)
  - Local Group Resources, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 51)
  - Lobbying for Abolition Guide, Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 52)
  - Medical Death Penalty Newsletter, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 53)
  - Meeting in Houston, ca.1994 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 54)
  - Member Questionnaire on Improving (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 55)
  - Members List, 1992-1994 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 56)
  - Memorandum, 1990; 1992-1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 57)
  - Merchandise Order Form, ca.1992; 1993-1994; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 58)
  - Midwest Regional Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 59)
  - Midwest Regional Leadership Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 60)
  - Midwest Regional News, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 61)
  - Midwest Regional News, 1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 62)
  - Midwest Region Death Penalty Update, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 63)
  - Midwest Region Newsletter, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 64)
  - Midwest Region Newsletter, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 65)
  - Midwest Region SDPAC, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 66)
  - Military, Security, Police Working Group, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 67)
  - Missouri Action Request, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 68)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 69)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 70)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 71)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 72)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 73)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 74)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 75)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 76)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 77)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1998 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 78)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 79)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1999 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 80)
  - Monthly Mailing, 2000 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 81)
  - Multi - Cultural Human Rights Symposium, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 82)
  - National Casework Program, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 83)
  - National Recruitment Drive, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Amnesty International), Folder 84)